A Guide to the Papers of the Institute of Public Affairs, University of Virginia, 1927-1953
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Correspondance and Miscellaneous Records (Box 54-145)
  - Federal Union 1941 (Box 113)
  - Rabbi Julian B. Feibelman 1941 (Box 113)
  - H. I. H. Archduke Felix of Austria 1941 (Box 113)
  - Frank Fenton 1941 (Box 113)
  - Louis Fischer 1941 (Box 113)
  - Michael T. Florinsky, Esq. 1941 (Box 113)
  - Foreign Policy Association 1941 (Box 113)
  - Forum Lecture Bureau Incorporated 1941 (Box 113)
  - Harry W. Frantz 1941 (Box 113)
  - Future Attentions 1941 (Box 113)
  - Future Attentions--Bibliography 1941 (Box 113)
  - Forsyth Glenn 1941 (Box 113)
  - John Patrick Gorman 1941 (Box 113)
  - Governor's Delegates--Suggested Appointments by the Gov. 1941 (Box 113)
  - C. Hartley Grattan 1941 (Box 113)
  - Dr. H. Duncan Hall 1941 (Box 113)
  - Harry Haller 1941 (Box 113)
  - Earl Harding 1941 (Box 113)
  - Dr. Edward Hambro 1941 (Box 113)
  - Bruce C. Hopper 1941 (Box 113)
  - Quincy Howe, Esq. 1941 (Box 113)
  - Dr. T. Y. Hu 1941 (Box 113)
  - Lewis Hanke 1941 (Box 113)
  - International Business Machines 1941 (Box 114)
  - Investment Bankers Association of America 1941 (Box 114)
  - Invoices 1941 (Box 114)
  - William C. Johnstone 1941 (Box 114)
  - "Keep America Out of War" Congress 1941 (Box 114)
  - Church Kenny 1941 (Box 114)
  - Hugh Knowlton 1941 (Box 114)
  - Dr. Z. Y. Kuo 1941 (Box 114)
  - Hon. Philip La Follette 1941 (Box 114)
  - Latin American Economic Institute 1941 (Box 114)
  - W. Jett Lauck 1941 (Box 114)
  - Morris S. Lazaron 1941 (Box 114)
  - The League for Fair Play, Incorporated 1941 (Box 114)
  - Lecture Bureaus 1941 (Box 114)
  - Dr. Emil Lengyel 1941 (Box 114)
  - Letters of Appreciation--Farmington, etc. 1941 (Box 114)
  - Letters of Appreciation to Faculty Panel Participants 1941 (Box 114)
  - Letters of Appreciation to Temporary Employees 1941 (Box 114)
  - Letters from Dillard 1941 (Box 114)
  - Library Letters--Reply to Circular Letter 1941 (Box 114)
  - Library Orders in Response to Form Letters 1941 (Box 114)
  - Ernest K. Lindley--Declined 1941[1950-1951] (Box 114)
  - Paul M. A. Linebarger, Esq. 1941 (Box 114)
  - Russell Lord, Esq. 1941 (Box 114)
  - Dr. E. S. de Lozada 1941 (Box 114)
  - Robert Lund 1941 (Box 114)
  - John MacCormac 1941 (Box 114)
  - Mailing List 1941 (Box 114)
  - George A. Mathews, Esq. 1941 (Box 114)
  - Dr. Karl A. Menninger 1941 (Box 114)
  - Count Roman Michalowski 1941 (Box 114)
  - Spencer Miller, Jr. 1941 (Box 114)
  - Miscellaneous 1941, 3 folders (Box 114)
  - Miscellaneous "A--Z" 1941, 20 folders (Box 115)
  - Edgar Ansel Mowrer 1941 (Box 115)
  - Malcolm Muir, Esq. 1941 (Box 115)
  - Lewis Mumford 1941 (Box 115)
  - Robert R. Nathan 1941 (Box 115)
  - National Association of Manufacturers 1941 (Box 115)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews 1941 (Box 115)
  - National Youth Administration 1941 (Box 115)
  - President John Lloyd Newcomb 1941 (Box 115)
  - Newspapers from which Press Clippings Were Taken 1927 (Box 115)
  - John F. Normano 1941 (Box 115)
  - Arthur Northwood, Jr.-- Time 's Lecturer's Bureau 1941 (Box 115)
  - Other Institutes 1941 (Box 115)
  - Dr. Jan Papanek 1941 (Box 115)
  - Payroll 1941 (Box 115)
  - Houston Peterson 1941 (Box 115)
  - Photographs 1941 (Box 115)
  - Hugh R. Pomeroy 1941 (Box 115)
  - Walter Prendergast 1941 (Box 115)
  - Press Clipping Service 1941 (Box 115)
  - Giovanni Previtali 1941 (Box 115)
  - Hon. James H. Price 1941 (Box 115)
  - Printer's Copy 1941 (Box 115)
  - Program Copy 1941 (Box 115)
  - Tentative Prospectus 1941 (Box 115)
  - Ida Pruett 1941 (Box 116)
  - Public Affairs Committee, Inc.--Displays 1941 (Box 116)
  - Publicity 1941 (Box 116)
  - Radio Talks 1941 (Box 116)
  - Radio Publicity--Cards from Audience 1941 (Box 116)
  - Receipts 1941 (Box 116)
  - Recommendations 1941 (Box 116)
  - Helen Dwight Reid 1941 (Box 116)
  - Requests for Proceedings: "A--R" 1941, 18 folders (Box 116)
  - Requests for Proceedings: "S--Z" 1941, 6 folders (Box 117)
  - Requests for Programs 1941 (Box 117)
  - Requisitions 1941 (Box 117)
  - Fernando de los Rios 1941 (Box 117)
  - Rockefeller Foundation 1941 (Box 117)
  - Rotary International 1941 (Box 117)
  - Rotary Letters of Reminder of 1941 Sessions 1941 (Box 117)
  - Beardsley Ruml, Esq. 1941, 1952 (Box 117)
  - Services 1941 (Box 117)
  - Count Carl Sforza 1941 (Box 117)
  - William L. Shirer, Esq. 1941 (Box 117)
  - Robert Aura Smith, Esq. 1941 (Box 117)
  - George Soule, Esq. 1941 (Box 117)
  - Statistics 1941 (Box 117)
  - Student Delegates 1941 (Box 117)
  - William P. Snavely 1941 (Box 117)
  - Suggestions for Programs 1941 (Box 117)
  - Suggestions for Speakers 1941 (Box 118)
  - Dr. Harry Stack Sullivan 1941 (Box 118)
  - Charles W. Taussig, Esq. 1941 (Box 118)
  - Edmond Taylor, Esq. 1941 (Box 118)
  - Henry J. Taylor, Esq. 1941 (Box 118)
  - Time & Fortune 1941 (Box 118)
  - Town Hall Meetings of the Air 1941 (Box 118)
  - Traveling Expense Vouchers 1941 (Box 118)
  - Dr. Rexford Guy Tugwell 1941 (Box 118)
  - University Press 1941 (Box 118)
  - Upsala College 1941 (Box 118)
  - Miss Freda Utley 1941 (Box 118)
  - Vertical File Service 1941 (Box 118)
  - Virginia Federation of Women's Clubs 1941 (Box 118)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review Letters 1941 (Box 118)
  - Albert Viton 1941 (Box 118)
  - John Martin Vorys 1941 (Box 118)
  - Washington Speakers Bureau, Inc. 1941 (Box 118)
  - Colonel Josiah Wedgwood 1941 (Box 118)
  - Western Union 1941 (Box 118)
  - John W. Wheeler-Bennett 1941 (Box 118)
  - Arthur P. Whitaker 1941 (Box 118)
  - Matthew Woll 1941 (Box 118)
  - Dr. David C. Wilson 1941 (Box 118)
  - William H. Wranek, Jr. 1941 (Box 118)
  - Station WRUL Broadcasts 1941 (Box 118)
  - William H. Wynne 1941 (Box 118)
  - Diosdado Yap 1941 (Box 118)
  - Anne C. Yates, Personal 1941 (Box 118)
  - James R. Young, Esq. 1941 (Box 118)
  - Accommodations 1942 (Box 119)
  - Hon. Dean G. Acheson 1942 (Box 119)
  - Alumni Fund 1942 (Box 119)
  - American Institute for Economic Research 1942 (Box 119)
  - American Management Association 1942 (Box 119)
  - Hon. Paul H. Appleby 1942 (Box 119)
  - Applications for Jobs 1942 (Box 119)
  - Application Blanks for School of Military Government 1942 (Box 119)
  - Autoscriptions to Reference Services 1942 (Box 119)
  - Sir Clive Baillieu 1942 (Box 119)
  - Hon. Alben W. Barkley 1942 (Box 119)
  - Stringfellow Barr 1942 (Box 119)
  - Dr. Samuel Flagg Bemis 1942 (Box 119)
  - Colonel Beukama 1942 (Box 119)
  - Rev. Beverly M. Boyd 1942 (Box 119)
  - Requests for Bibliographies 1942 (Box 119)
  - Andrew J. Biemiller 1942 (Box 119)
  - Richard M. Bissell, Jr. 1942 (Box 119)
  - Thomas C. Blaisdell 1942 (Box 119)
  - Board of Visitors Committee 1942 (Box 119)
  - Book Display 1942 (Box 119)
  - Hugh Borton 1942 (Box 119)
  - Bound Volumes Sent Through Alderman Library 1942 (Box 119)
  - Brigadier G. K. Bourne 1942 (Box 119)
  - Bjarne Braatoy 1942 (Box 119)
  - British Library of Information 1942 (Box 119)
  - Brown-Morrison Company 1942 (Box 119)
  - Budget 1942 (Box 119)
  - Bursar 1942 (Box 119)
  - Caldwell-Sites 1942 (Box 119)
  - Capitol Seating Company 1942 (Box 119)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace 1942 (Box 119)
  - Stuart Chase 1942 (Box 119)
  - Dr. Melvin de Chazeau 1942 (Box 119)
  - Leo M. Cherne 1942 (Box 119)
  - Colonnade Club 1942 (Box 119)
  - Committee to Study the Organization of Peace 1942 (Box 119)
  - Concerns Newly Solicited--Who Contributed 1942 (Box 119)
  - Concerns Newly Solicited--Who Did Not Contribute 1942 (Box 119)
  - Continuance of Insitute--Recommendations 1942 (Box 119)
  - Contributions 1942, 6 folders (Box 120)
  - Firms Contributing in Previous Years Who Did Not Contribute 1942 (Box 120)
  - Former Contributors 1942 (Box 120)
  - Contribution and Pledge List 1942 (Box 120)
  - Cooperating Organizations 1942 (Box 120)
  - Percy E. Corbett 1942 (Box 120)
  - Father John F. Corbin 1942 (Box 120)
  - Dr. William Wilson Cumberland 1942 (Box 120)
  - Virginius Dabney, Esq. 1942 (Box 120)
  - Jonathan Daniels 1942 (Box 120)
  - Lambert Davis, Esq. 1942 (Box 120)
  - Gov. Colgate W. Darden 1942 (Box 120)
  - Dr. Charles K. Davenport 1942 (Box 120)
  - Watson Davis 1942 (Box 120)
  - Mrs. Vera Micheles Dean 1942 (Box 120)
  - H. C. Dillard's Letters to and from Contributors 1942 (Box 120)
  - Hardy C. Dillard--Personal folder 1942 (Box 120)
  - Displays for Cooperating Organizationns 1942 (Box 120)
  - "Do you know that" 1942 (Box 120)
  - Nicholas Doman 1942 (Box 120)
  - Leonard Doob 1942 (Box 120)
  - Harold A. Downs 1942 (Box 120)
  - Dr. Peter F. Drucker 1942 (Box 120)
  - Colonel R. Ernest Dupuy 1942 (Box 120)
  - Thomas H. Elliot 1942 (Box 120)
  - William Yandell Elliot 1942 (Box 120)
  - Enquiries (A--Z) 1942, 2 folders (Box 120)
  - Dr. Brooks Emeny 1942 (Box 120)
  - Estimates 1942 (Box 120)
  - A. H. Feller 1942 (Box 121)
  - Harry W. Frantz 1942 (Box 121)
  - Foreign Policy Association 1942 (Box 121)
  - Future Attentions 1942 (Box 121)
  - Stuart G. Gibboney, Esq. 1942 (Box 121)
  - Matthew Gordon 1942 (Box 121)
  - Governor's Delegates 1942 (Box 121)
  - Allen T. Gwathmey 1942 (Box 121)
  - Hale--Introductions 1942 (Box 121)
  - Walter D. Head 1942 (Box 121)
  - Thomas Henry 1942 (Box 121)
  - Dr. Duncan C. Hyde 1942 (Box 121)
  - Invitation Letters--Congratulatory 1942 (Box 121)
  - Madge Harper Kottal 1942 (Box 121)
  - Theodore J. Kreps 1942 (Box 121)
  - Robert K. Lamb 1942 (Box 121)
  - Harold D. Lasswell 1942 (Box 121)
  - Dr. Walter H. C. Laves 1942 (Box 121)
  - Dr. W. Jett Lauck 1942 (Box 121)
  - Lecture Bureaus 1942 (Box 121)
  - Lt. Colonel L. B. Lent 1942 (Box 121)
  - Letters--$1.00 1942 (Box 121)
  - Letters to Pledge 1942 (Box 121)
  - Ernest K. Lindley 1942 (Box 121)
  - List of Acceptances 1942 (Box 121)
  - List of Registered Members 1942 (Box 121)
  - Listings in Volumes and Magazines 1942 (Box 121)
  - Local People Previously Unsolicited 1942 (Box 121)
  - Louis P. Lochner 1942 (Box 121)
  - Dr. Lewis L. Lorwin 1942 (Box 121)
  - Captain Leland P. Lovette 1942 (Box 121)
  - Isador Lubin 1942 (Box 121)
  - Luce's Press Clipping Bureau 1942 (Box 121)
  - Archibald MacLeish 1942 (Box 121)
  - Stephen McDonough 1942 (Box 121)
  - Lt. Commander William M. McGovern 1942 (Box 121)
  - Brigadier Gen. Frank J. McSherry 1942 (Box 121)
  - Mailing List 1942 (Box 121)
  - Maps of the University 1942 (Box 121)
  - George N. Mathews 1942 (Box 121)
  - Count Roman Michalowski 1942 (Box 121)
  - Hon. Walter Nash 1942 (Box 121)
  - Miscellaneous "A--Z" 1942, 22 folders (Box 122)
  - Robert Nathan 1942 (Box 122)
  - National Assn. of Manufacturers 1942 (Box 122)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews 1942 (Box 122)
  - Dr. John Lloyd Newcomb 1942 (Box 122)
  - Dr. John Lloyd Newcomb's Letters from Contributors 1942 (Box 122)
  - Hoffman Nickerson 1942 (Box 122)
  - Peter Odegard 1942 (Box 122)
  - Other Institutes 1942 (Box 122)
  - Contract with Paces 1942 (Box 122)
  - Pamphlet Orders 1942 (Box 122)
  - Pamphlet Orders--Filled 1942 (Box 122)
  - Pamphlet Orders--Requested 1942 (Box 122)
  - Payroll 1942 (Box 122)
  - Amos J. Peaslee 1942 (Box 122)
  - Personal Expenditures--Insitute 1942 (Box 122)
  - Photographs 1942 (Box 122)
  - Mr. Orville S. Poland 1942 (Box 122)
  - Hugh R. Pomeroy 1942 (Box 122)
  - Lt. Colonel S. P. Poole 1942 (Box 122)
  - Dr. Henry Alford Porter 1942 (Box 122)
  - Press Clippings 1942 (Box 122)
  - Printers Copy 1942 (Box 122)
  - Program 1942 (Box 122)
  - Program Copy 1942 (Box 122)
  - Publicity 1942 (Box 122)
  - Dr. Don Luis Quintanilla 1942 (Box 122)
  - Radio Publicity 1942 (Box 122)
  - Receipts 1942 (Box 122)
  - Reports on Session 1942, 3 folders (Box 123)
  - Requests for Proceedings: "A-K" 1942, 11 folders (Box 123)
  - Requests for Proceedings: "L-Z" 1942, 13 folders (Box 124)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller 1942 (Box 124)
  - Dean Walter S. Rodman 1942 (Box 124)
  - Rotary International 1942 (Box 124)
  - Henry Rowell 1942 (Box 124)
  - Sample Material 1942 (Box 124)
  - Dr. Frederick L. Schuman 1942 (Box 124)
  - William L. Schurz 1942 (Box 124)
  - Services 1942 (Box 124)
  - Prof. James T. Shotwell 1942 (Box 124)
  - Dan Shumate-Press Releases 1942 (Box 124)
  - Rabbi Abraham Shusterman 1942 (Box 124)
  - Maj. Nathaniel Silshee 1942 (Box 124)
  - C. Bascom Slemp 1942 (Box 124)
  - Dr. Tipton R. Snavely 1942 (Box 124)
  - Branch Spaulding 1942 (Box 124)
  - Letters to Speaker's Bureaus 1942 (Box 124)
  - Speakers Declined 1942, 2 folders (Box 124)
  - Speakers Invited 1942 (Box 125)
  - Nicholas J. Spykman 1942 (Box 125)
  - Standing Orders 1942 (Box 125)
  - Suggestions for Speakers 1942 (Box 125)
  - Suggestions for Program 1942 (Box 125)
  - Maj. Gen. A. D. Surles 1942 (Box 125)
  - Dr. W. Francis G. Swann 1942 (Box 125)
  - Henry J. Taylor 1942 (Box 125)
  - Hon. Elbert D. Thomas 1942 (Box 125)
  - Dr. Lorwin A. Thompso 1942 (Box 125)
  - Lt. Colonel Paul W. Thompson 1942 (Box 125)
  - Time, Inc. 1942 (Box 125)
  - Town Hall Meetings of the Air 1942 (Box 125)
  - Traveling Expense Vouchers 1942 (Box 125)
  - Arthur R. Upgren 1942 (Box 125)
  - Upsula College 1942 (Box 125)
  - Vertical File Service 1942 (Box 125)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1942 (Box 125)
  - Thomas J. Wallner 1942 (Box 125)
  - Western Union 1942 (Box 125)
  - John W. Wheeler-Bennett 1942 (Box 125)
  - Paul W. White 1942 (Box 125)
  - Miss Mary Winslow 1942 (Box 125)
  - H. W. Weigert 1942 (Box 125)
  - Prof. A. Curtis Wilgus 1942 (Box 125)
  - Arnold Wolfers 1942 (Box 125)
  - William H. Wranch, Jr. 1942 (Box 125)
  - David McCord Wright 1942 (Box 125)
  - Anne C. Yates 1942 (Box 125)
  - Disbursements 1943 (Box 125)
  - Institute of Public Affairs 1943 (Box 125)
  - Receipts 1943 (Box 125)
  - Institute of Public Affairs 1949 (Box 126)
  - Lecture Bureau [1949] (Box 126)
  - Other Institutes 1949-1952 (Box 126)
  - Dr. Mehdi Ben Aboud 1952 (Box 126)
  - Abstract 1953 (Box 126)
  - Accommodations [1950-1951] 1953 (Box 126)
  - Accommodations--Rooms for Visitors 1950 (Box 126)
  - Account Book--Institute 1950-1952 (Box 126)
  - Dean Acheson--Secretary of State [1950-1951] (Box 126)
  - Hon. Dean Acheson--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 126)
  - Ad Hoc Committee Meeting 1951 (Box 126)
  - Roscoe S. Adams [1950-1951] (Box 126)
  - Administration and Budget 1953 (Box 126)
  - Admission Tickets 1953 (Box 126)
  - Advanced Students to Help with the Institute [1950-1951] (Box 126)
  - Advisory Committee 1950-1953 (Box 126)
  - Martin Agronsky 1952 (Box 126)
  - Alumni Office 1950 (Box 126)
  - American Association of University Women 1950-1951 (Box 126)
  - American Broadcasting Company (Agronsky and Frederick) 1952 (Box 126)
  - American Federation of Labor [1950-1951] (Box 126)
  - Stanley Andrews [1950-1951] (Box 126)
  - Announcement and Tentative Program [1950-1951] (Box 126)
  - Announcements 1950 (Box 127)
  - Applicants for Jobs 1952-1953 (Box 127)
  - Ellis G. Arnall 1952 (Box 127)
  - Thurman Arnold [1950-1951] (Box 127)
  - Arrangements--General 1952-1953 (Box 127)
  - Atlantic Union Committee 1950 (Box 127)
  - Franklin G. Balch [1950-1951] (Box 127)
  - Stringfellow Barr--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 127)
  - Alan Barth 1953 (Box 127)
  - Gov. John S. Battle [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 127)
  - Dr. James P. Baxter, III. [1950-1951] (Box 127)
  - Ales Bebler, Esq. 1952 (Box 127)
  - The Belgian Ambassador [1950-1951] (Box 127)
  - Jean Pierre Benard [1950-1951] (Box 127)
  - William Benton--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 127)
  - Dr. Lloyd V. Berkner [1950-1951] (Box 127)
  - Adolf A. Berle, Jr. 1952 (Box 127)
  - Hon. Francis Biddle 1952 (Box 127)
  - Bills 1952-1953 (Box 127)
  - Bills Paid 1953-1954 (Box 127)
  - Biographical Sketches [1950-1951] (Box 127)
  - Biographical Sketches--Speakers and Participants 1951 (Box 127)
  - Binding--Institute Proceedings 1952 (Box 128)
  - Barry Bingham [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Richard M. Bissel [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Guy Blalock-Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Board of Visitors [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Hon. Charles E. Bohlen 1952 (Box 128)
  - Arch Booth [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Dr. Hugh Borton [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Bound Copies-Checks Received 1951 (Box 128)
  - Bound Copies-List of Orders Received [1950] (Box 128)
  - Bound Copies--Proceedings [1950] (Box 128)
  - Bound Copies-Proceedings 1951 (Box 128)
  - Bound Copy List 1953 (Box 128)
  - Dr. Gordon Bowles [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Thomas Boushall [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Charles F. Brannan--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Irving Brant, Esq. 1952 (Box 128)
  - Parke C. Brinkley--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - British Embassy [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - British Information Services [1950] (Box 128)
  - Broadcasting [1950] (Box 128)
  - Dr. Detlev W. Bronk [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Brookings Institution 1950 (Box 128)
  - James A. Brownlow--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - David K. E. Bruce 1952 (Box 128)
  - Dr. Marshall Brucer--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Mrs. J. L. Blair Buck [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Budget 1950-1952 (Box 128)
  - Buildings and Grounds 1950-1953 (Box 128)
  - Franklin L. Burdette [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - H. L. Burrough [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Bursar's Office 1951 (Box 128)
  - Bursar's Office--Statement of Receipts, Disbursements and Balances 1953 (Box 128)
  - Dr. Vannevar Bush [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 128)
  - Hon. Harry Flood Byrd [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 128)
  - Hon. James F. Byrnes [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 128)
  - Henry A. Byroade [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Dr. John Cady--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Dr. Robert Calkins [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Dr. Robert Calkins [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Harold Callender [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Ned Calmer--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 128)
  - Kenneth Campbell [1953] (Box 128)
  - James B. Carey--Secretary 1952 (Box 129)
  - Dr. William G. Carleton [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Dr. O. C. Carmichael--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Carnegie Endowment for the Advancement of Teaching [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace 1950-1952 (Box 129)
  - Certificate Credit to Institute Attendants [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Dr. Amiya Chakravarty [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - John Chamberlain [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Dr. Dwight W. Chapman [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Charlottesville Ministers 1950-1953 (Box 129)
  - Charlottesville Pastors 1952 (Box 129)
  - Marquis Childs [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 129)
  - C. I. O. [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Circular Letters 1953 (Box 129)
  - Circulars--Books 1951-1952 (Box 129)
  - City Manager Letters 1952 (Box 129)
  - Hon. Gordon R. Clapp [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Gen. Lucius B. Clay--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Clippings 1951 (Box 129)
  - Clippings and Program--"Outlook for the Free World" 1953 (Box 129)
  - Prof. Paul H. Clyde [1953] (Box 129)
  - C. Francis Cocke [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Benjamin Cohen [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - David L. Cohn 1952 (Box 129)
  - John H. Colburn [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 129)
  - Dr. R. Taylor Cole--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Columbus Town Meeting 1952 (Box 129)
  - Committee Meetings--Minutes 1951-1953 (Box 129)
  - Contributions [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Contributions Made Through Dr. John Lloyd Newcomb 1951 (Box 129)
  - Contributions Made Through Mr. Zehmer 1951 (Box 129)
  - Contributions--Other Than Subscribers to 1951 Bound Copies 1951 (Box 129)
  - Contributions Solicited 1953 (Box 129)
  - Contributors 1953 (Box 129)
  - Contributors--1952 Institute 1953 (Box 129)
  - Alistair Cooke [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Dr. James B. Conant [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Dr. John S. Cooper--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - John J. Corson--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 129)
  - Edward S. Corwin 1952 (Box 130)
  - Gardner Cowles 1952 (Box 130)
  - Nelson C. Cruikshank--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Dr. Dewey Daane [1953] (Box 130)
  - Virginius Dabney [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Virginius Dabney--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Clifford C. Dancer 1952 (Box 130)
  - Dr. Royden Dangerfield--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Jonathan Daniels--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - President Colgate W. Darden, Jr. 1950-1953 (Box 130)
  - Hon. Jean Daridan [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Dr. Taraknath Das [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Russell W. Davenport [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Watson Davis [1953] (Box 130)
  - Mrs. Vera M. Dean--Declined 1950 (Box 130)
  - Mrs. Vera M. Dean 1951 (Box 130)
  - Gontron de Juniac 1951 (Box 130)
  - Delegates 1952-1953 (Box 130)
  - Delegates--Armed Services and Academies 1953 (Box 130)
  - Delegates--Armed Services Branches 1952 (Box 130)
  - Delegates--Governors, Embassies and Students 1952 (Box 130)
  - Delegates--League of Women Voters 1953 (Box 130)
  - George V. Denny 1953 (Box 130)
  - Department of State--Division of Public Liaison 1951 (Box 130)
  - Department of State--Speakers [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Deposits in Bursar's Office--Checks and Cash 1950-1951 (Box 130)
  - Deposits in Bursar's Office 1951-1953 (Box 130)
  - Wallace Deuel [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Dr. Edward T. Dickinson--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Hardy C. Dillard--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Director's Report on Institute Session and Announcement 1950-1951 (Box 130)
  - Hon. Michael V. Disalle [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Dr. Bayard Dodge 1952 (Box 130)
  - Dr. Frederick R. Dolbeare [1950-1951] (Box 130)
  - Donations 1951 (Box 130)
  - Dormitory Reservations and Housing 1953 (Box 130)
  - Hon. Lewis W. Douglas 1952 (Box 131)
  - Senator Paul Douglas--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Peter Drucker--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Hon. James H. Duff, Senator [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 131)
  - Allen Dulles--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Hon. John Foster Dulles--Declined [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 131)
  - Dr. Edward M. Earle 1952 (Box 131)
  - Dr. Rowland A. Egger [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Dr. Milton S. Eisenhower--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Dr. W. Y. Elliott--Declined 1941,1950-1952 (Box 131)
  - Herbert Elliston--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Embassies--Replies from 1952 (Box 131)
  - Embassy--Acceptances 1952 (Box 131)
  - Embassy Representatives 1952 (Box 131)
  - John K. Emmerson [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Employment--Temporary [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Entertainment--1953 Session 1953 (Box 131)
  - Equipment Borrowed 1952 (Box 131)
  - Mark F. Ethridge [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 131)
  - Expense Accounts 1951-1953 (Box 131)
  - Extension Division 1953 (Box 131)
  - Faculty Donations and Pledges 1953 (Box 131)
  - Merle Fainsod [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Benjamin F. Fairless 1952 (Box 131)
  - Dr. N. Saifpour Fatemi 1952 (Box 131)
  - Favorable Comments 1951 (Box 131)
  - Federal Security Agency 1951 (Box 131)
  - Hon. Abraham H. Feller--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Dr. Alfred H. Ferbach--Accepted [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 131)
  - Frank L. Fernbach 1952 (Box 131)
  - File References 1952 (Box 131)
  - J. G. N. Finley--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Dr. Harold H. Fisher 1951 (Box 131)
  - Hon. Ralph Edward Flanders--Declined [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 131)
  - Miss Doris Fleeson [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Dr. Arthur S. Flemming 1951 (Box 131)
  - Foreign Policy Association 1950-1953 (Box 131)
  - Form Letters [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Former Institute Speakers [1950-1951] (Box 131)
  - Forms--General 1950-1953 (Box 132)
  - Dr. Constantin Fournadjeff [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Henry H. Fowler 1952 (Box 132)
  - Prof. Wm. T. R. Fox--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Sir Oliver Franks--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Miss Pauline Frederick 1951-1952 (Box 132)
  - Max Freedman [1953] (Box 132)
  - Freedoms Foundation 1953 (Box 132)
  - Freedoms Foundation Award--Valley Forge, Pa. 1952 (Box 132)
  - Carl J. Freidrich, Esq. 1952 (Box 132)
  - Alfred Friendly--Accepted 1950-1953 (Box 132)